

# **Michael Gray**

**Enterprise Web Developer** 

## **Contact**

Phone: 501-247-6443

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/michael-gray-dev

Website: www.michaeldgray.com

Email: mgray2@ualr.edu

#### Greetings,

I have a great passion for web development and media content creation, and based on the requirements and aspects of the position, I feel as though I would be an ideal candidate. With over 9 years of experience I have just about worked all levels of IT field and that help make me a solid individual for web development major in the Bachelor program at UA Little Rock.

I feel my skillsets and ability to learn technologies and work well wit others makes me a great asset for any team. I am willing to take on any challenge that will increase my skillset and knowledge base to become a solid web developer.

I would like verymuch to discuss opportunities with your company. To schedule an interview, please call me at 501-247-6443.

Thank you for taking the time to review my resume. I look foward to talking to you.

Sincerely,

Michael Gray



## **Profile**

With more than 8 years of IT expereince including a Bachelors Degree major in Web Design/Development. I am a well rounded skillset personality that has experience using HTML,CSS,Javascript along with using backend PHP language as well. My current position as a Enterprise Web Developer we do a combination of CMS management and PHP applications to keep the campus websites responsive and maintain PHP to collect data to a databse.

### **Contact**

Phone: 501-247-6443

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/michael-gray-dev

Website: www.michaeldgray.com

Email: mgray2@ualr.edu

#### Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

PHP

Wordpress

Linux

Windows

Troubleshooting

#### **Education**

**University of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

8/2020 - 5/2024

**Bachelor of Arts** 

Web Design & Development

**Pulaski Technical College** 

8/2013 - 12/2015

**Associates Degree** 

Comp Info Systems: Networking

#### Experience

**Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

Enterprise Web Developer 04/2022 – Present

**Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

Systems Administrator 06/2019 – 04/2022

**Windstream Communications** 

Network Analyst 04/2019 – 06/2019

SCA Pharmaceutical

Network Administrator

04/2019 - 06/2019

**AFMC** 

IT support Specialist 06/2016 – 02/2019

**Dept of Human Services** 

**Unified Comunication Specialist** 

06/2015 - 06/2016

**Windstream Communications** 

Network Analyst II

12/2012 - 04/2015